ALINA SHAIKH

Account Manager & Client Servicing

Experienced professional with a Master's in Events and Public Relations and a Bachelor's in Mass Media. Transitioned from business development in employee engagement to Client Servicing and Key Account Manager in advertising. Expert in client relations, strategic account management, and successful campaign execution. Blend academic insights with practical industry experience for effective communication and strategic planning.

Contact



8369950512

Mumbai, India

Education

 Masters in Event Management and Public Relations
2018 - 2020
NAEMD, Mumbai, India

Bachelor of Mass Media
2015 - 2018
SNGC, Mumbai, India

Core Skills

- Team Building and Coordination
- Account and Community Management
- Research and Development
- Strategic Account Management:
- Client Relationship Management:
- · Adaptability and Problem-Solving

Soft Skills

- Delivering Positive Customer Engagement
- Excellent Communication
- Extreme Accountability and Ownership
- Collaborative
- Highly Organized

Languages

- English
- Hindi
- Marathi

Hobbies

- Art
- Movies
- Music
- Travelling
- Reading

Work Experience

One Hand Clap

Client Servicing & Key Account Manager May 2023 - Currently Working

- Develop and implement strategic plans for key client accounts - CoinDCX and Swiggy Genie, ensuring alignment with their objectives and industry trends.
- Work with internal colleagues to devise campaign that meets the client's brief and budget
- Utilize excellent communication skills to liaise effectively with clients and internal cross-functional teams, ensuring a seamless workflow and alignment with client expectations..
- Strategizing ideas for social media

ExtraMile Engage

Client Servicing & Business Development Lead March 2021 – May 2023

- Communicate with Clients to understand their requirement
- Work closely with the operations team and conveying the client's requirement to the team.
- Closed long term agreements through skillful negotiation
- Managed escalated client enquiries with exceptional professionalism and enthusiasm
- Planned and executed new strategies to increase sales.
- Developed team communications and information for meetings.

Live101

Client Servicing & Account Data Manager September 2019 – December 2019

- Resolved customer questions and issues efficiently to reach mutually beneficial solutions.
- Mentored juniors on methods of industry best practices for outstanding service and retention.
- Improved service quality and increased sales by developing a strong knowledge of the company's products and services.
- Communicated regularly with team members to maintain clearly defined expectations.